（左門）早いな。　それに多い。→
That was quick.
And so many.
本格的な攻勢はあっても
まだ先だと思っていたが→
I expected a full-on attack, but not this soon.
Apparently, someone in the government is competent.
政府に切れ者がいたか…。→
それとも　これも
はじまりの樹がもたらす→
Or is this also due to the princess's monstrous luck, thanks to the Tree of Genesis?
姫様の強運か…。
Very well, Princess.
ならば　姫様
今日で　その運　尽きさせましょう。
Today, let us put an end to your good fortune.
（不破真広）軍の連中　そろそろ→
Looks like the army's about to do their thing.
おっぱじめるつもりらしいぜ。
Even if they start their attack,
（葉風・通信）
始めたところで　通常兵器では→
it could take normal weapons weeks to break through the barrier.
結界を破るまで
何週間かかるか分からんぞ。→
They'll probably run out of ammunition first.
その前に
弾薬が尽きるだろうがな。
（葉風）お前たちは
魔具を１０個ほど準備しろ。→
You two should prepare around ten talismans.
それで　なんとか
結界内に侵入できるだろう。
That should be enough to get you through the barrier.
（葉風）
雌雄を決するときが来たな　左門。
Time to see how this fight ends, Samon.
（滝川吉野）真広。
ん？
Mahiro...
Do you think anything will change from now on?
今日で　何かが変わると思うか？
んなもん
俺には　どうでもいいことだな。
Doesn't matter to me.
（心の声）≪いまだに…→
Even now...
いまだに思い出すたび
何もかもが疑わしくなる≫
Even now, when I think back on it,
I became suspicious of everything.
≪一体　なぜ信じられるのか…→
I didn't know how I was supposed to believe
これで　愛花が死んでいると≫
that this meant Aika was dead.
（回想）((どうして　冷たいんだ？))
Why are you so cold?
行くぞ→
Let's go.
愛花を殺したヤツを突き止めにな。
To find the one who killed Aika!
Episode 8
The Hour to Suppress
the Princess
Defense Force, Marines, Air Force, Navy Joint Exercise
According to the Ministry of Defense,
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（アナウンサー）防衛省によりますと→
the military exercises being conducted at Mt. Fuji's base are the first large-scale joint exercises
今回の富士山麓における
国防軍の演習は→
初の陸・海・空　３国防軍による
大規模なものとなっており→
involving Marines, Navy, and Air Force.
報道関係者
および　一般人の立ち入りは→
The press, as well as civilians, are strictly forbidden to enter the premises.
厳しく制限されております。
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（アナウンサー）
防衛省は今後も　軍の統合運用を→
The Ministry of Defense issued a statement that these joint exercises are likely to be held again in the future.
念頭に置いた演習を
実施していく考えのようです。
（山本）ふっ
これが最後にならなきゃいいけど。
Hopefully, this won't be the end.
（通信）観測ヘリの映像　回せ！
（通信）目標上空到達まで２分！
（通信）ＣＩＣ指示の目標！
（通信）発射弾数　２つ！
Company 1, 2, and 3, ready your fire!
第１　第２　第３中隊
効力射　用意！
撃て～！
Fire!
なんつって。
Just kidding.
ドカーーン！
ドカン！　ドカン　ドカン！
始まったみたいだ！
急ぐぞ！
Looks like they've started.
Let's hurry!
さあ　魔法使いども→
Come on, mages...
その殻の中から出てきなさい。
Come out from under that shell.
（左門）哲馬
軍の攻撃に対する指揮を任せる。→
Tetsuma,
I'm leaving you in charge of countering the army's attack.
Continue with the revival ritual, but protect the Tree of Exodus at all costs.
復活の儀式を続けつつ
絶園の樹の安全を優先。
結界の迷彩効果を切ってもいい。
You may remove the barrier's camouflage.
Redirect that power to increase the barrier's resistance to attack.
その活力を　衝撃防御に回せ。
絶園の樹の姿→
There is no further need to hide
もはや隠すこともない。
the Tree of Exodus's existence.
There's been a change within the target.
（宇津井・通信）目標に変化あり。
（早河）あれが…。
That's...
≪なんだ!?
≫確認　急げ！
出たわね　絶園の樹。
So there you are,
Tree of Exodus.
（哲馬・通信）
左門殿　何者かが　結界に干渉。→
Mr. Samon, someone is meddling with the barrier.
They're trying to break through.
侵入を図っています。
The battle has just begun, Princess.
姫様　勝負は　これからです。
We made it through the barrier, Hakaze.
結界を抜けたぞ　葉風。
（葉風・通信）ああ。
All right.
（葉風）これで
左門に　完全に気付かれた。→
Then Samon knows you're there.
But there's no reason for you to run or hide.
だが　逃げ隠れする必要はない。→
Head straight for the Tree of Exodus.
まっすぐ　絶園の樹に向かえ。
あと一手…→
Just one more move...
それで詰みだ。
and then checkmate.
All forces have finished their initial attack.
（通信士）
各部隊　第１次攻撃　終了！
Report damage to target.
（指揮官・通信）
目標への効果　確認！
（宇津井）指揮所へ
目標への効果　確認できず。→
Command, we are unable to confirm any damage sustained by the target.
戦車　および
戦闘車による近接攻撃に移る。→
We will engage the target at close range with tanks and attack vehicles.
（通信）送れ！
（通信）了解！
Attack!
Roger.
あの障壁らしきものを
どうにかせんかぎりは→
I assume it'll just be a waste of ammunition
弾の無駄だろうがな。
if we don't deal with that barrier.
魔法の力　これほどとは…。
To think that magic could be so powerful...
（山本）
軍の連中　焦ってきてるな。→
The army guys are starting to panic.
They may be up against mages,
でも　魔法使いっていっても→
but the mages have no offensive magic.
ヤツらに　攻撃魔法みたいなものは
存在しない。
だから　今は
ひたすら攻めてりゃいいのよ。
So the army should just keep attacking.
（男たち）戻れ　戻れ　戻れ→
Return! Return! Return! Return!
戻れ　戻れ　戻れ…。
（哲馬）
今は　外の攻撃を無視しろ！→
Ignore the outside attacks!
結界は　まだ安定している！→
The barrier remains stable.
その間に　できるだけ
儀式を進めておくのだ！
Proceed with the ritual as much as possible during this time!
（哲馬）≪とは言っても
想定以上の攻勢だ≫
However, their offensive is far more aggressive than predicted.
≪あまりに受けすぎれば
復活後の絶園の樹の制御に→
Sustaining damage at this rate could hinder our control of the revived Tree of Exodus.
支障が出てしまう…≫
ボゥン！　ボゥン！
ボゥン！
バシューー！
樽？
≫ザッザッザッ…（足音）
A barrel?
葉風　髪が長くて　刀持った→
Hakaze,
some guy wearing a stand-collar shirt with long hair and a sword is here.
詰め襟野郎が出てきたぞ。
（葉風・通信）
左門で間違いなかろう。→
Must be Samon.
そのまま近づけ
私の声が届く所まで。
Keep moving forward,
so that my voice will reach him.
（左門）よく来た　少年。→
Welcome, young men.
我が名は　鎖部左門。→
My name is Kusaribe Samon.
古き一族
鎖部に連なる者を代表して→
I stand before you to represent the ancient clan of the Kusaribe.
今　ここに立っている。→
少年
お前たちに　名乗る名はあるか？
Young men, do you have names?
へっ　少年Ａと　ほか一名でいいさ。
Just call us "young man A" and "other one."
We aren't the ones here to talk to you.
話があるのは
俺らじゃないからな。
（葉風・通信）久しいな　左門。→
It's been a while, Samon.
４か月ぶりになるか。
変わりなくやっているようだな。
Four months now?
Seems you're doing well.
姫様こそ→
You too, Princess,
despite being so far away.
（通信）
遠く隔たっていても　お変わりなく。
左門　すでに分かっていよう。→
Samon, I'm sure that you're already aware
（通信）
この者に持たせてある魔具は→
that the talisman I gave this young man
すでに　我が魔法の効果範囲だ。→
contains the full extent of my magic.
As soon as he uses it, your control over the Tree of Exodus will be disrupted.
使用すれば
すぐさま　絶園の樹の制御は狂い→
The barrier will break, and there will be a wave of destruction that only I can stop.
結界は破れ
私でなければ収拾できぬ→
破壊の嵐が
その一帯に発生しよう。→
If that were to happen, you would have no choice but to bring me back.
そうなれば　貴様は
私を　そこに戻すしかなくなる。→
降伏しろ　左門。
Surrender, Samon.
魔具を発動させる前に→
Return me there before I invoke the talisman.
おとなしく私を　そこに戻せ。→
（通信）私が　私の魔具を持つ者を→
The outcome of this battle was decided when my men were able to penetrate the barrier and bring in the talisman.
そこに送り込めた時点で
勝負は決した。→
貴様は　よくやった。
なのに　往生際も悪く→
You've done well.
But you're unreasonably stubborn, resulting in needless casualties.
いらぬ被害を出しても
しかたあるまい。
降伏するのは
プライドが許さねぇっていうなら→
If you're going to say you're too proud to surrender,
I can pull the trigger right now.
すぐに　こいつを引いてやるぜ。
（左門）
引いて　世界を滅ぼすのか？→
You'd pull the trigger and destroy the world?
Without the Tree of Exodus,
絶園の樹なくして
この世は守れんぞ。
you'll never save this world.
世界を滅ぼすのは
あの絶園の樹の力でしょう？
Isn't the Tree of Exodus the one with the potential to destroy the world?
現に　どれだけのものが壊れ→
How many things have been broken,
and how many lives have already been lost?
どれだけの人が
死んだと思ってるんです？
（左門）聞いてないのか？
それらの現象は→
Didn't you know?
All of those incidents derive from
はじまりの樹が
絶園の樹を復活させぬため→
the Tree of Genesis's attempts to stop the Tree of Exodus's revival,
by ensuring that if anyone tries to collect the fruit, massive casualties will ensue.
果実を集めようとすれば
大きな被害が出るよう→
仕組んだものだ。
えっ？
Huh?
（左門）この世界を滅ぼすのは
絶園の樹の復活ではない。→
It is not the revival of the Tree of Exodus that will destroy this world.
はじまりの樹の覚醒だ。→
It is the awakening of the Tree of Genesis.
それを防ぎ
この世界を救えるのは→
The only thing that can prevent it and save this world
ただ絶園の樹のみ。
あの大樹こそが→
is the Tree of Exodus.
That great tree is our one and only sword of hope!
我らにとって　たった一つ
希望の剣なのだ。
（潤一郎）
この世界は　はじまりの樹が→
This world was created while the Tree of Genesis slumbered.
眠っている間に生まれた
ある意味　不完全な世界だ。
And in a way, it is an incomplete world.
Although the world is under the influence of the Tree of Genesis,
はじまりの樹の力が
及んでいるとはいえ→
there are faults in its logic, and it's undeniably unstable.
その理には隙があるし
不安定なのも否定できない。→
つまり　この世界は正しくない。→
Meaning that this world isn't right.
だから
はじまりの樹が目覚めれば→
Thus, when the Tree of Genesis wakes,
まず　この世界を
完全で正しいものに造り直す。
this world will be recreated into its rightful and complete form.
そのため
この世界は　一度　消滅する。
To do that, the current world must first be destroyed.
（左門）はじまりの樹が
その力を発するのに→
You must know what the Tree of Genesis requires in order to exert its power.
何が必要か知っていよう。→
力の代償に捧げるものを。
What must be offered for that power...
高度な文明の産物。
（左門）そう。→
The high-level products of civilization.
Exactly.
To recreate this world, the required number of such products will be
この世界を　完全に造り直すために
必要とされる文明の産物は→
想像を絶する量に上ろう。→
greater than anyone can imagine.
はじまりの樹が目覚めれば→
If the Tree of Genesis awakens,
it will feed on every civilization in this world.
今　地球上にある
文明という文明を食い尽くすぞ。→
そうなれば
人類は　１億と生き残れまい。→
Humanity will be decimated.
そのうえ　生物のあり方そのものが
書き換えられ→
It is even possible that life as we know it will be remade,
leading to the extinction of all existing species.
現存する　すべての種族は
滅びる可能性もある。
When I learned how magic works, something felt off.
≪魔法の説明を聞いたとき
何か違和感があった≫
≪そうだ　鎖部の魔法は→
I get it now...
The Kusaribe magic may protect the world's logic.
理を守るかもしれない≫
However,
≪でも　引き換えに
文明をリセットする→
it is also a terrible power, with the ability to reset civilization itself.
恐ろしい力でもあるんだ≫
だから　近代になって→
That's why, in the present day,
鎖部一族の　ごく一部で
考えられるようになった。→
a handful of Kusaribe came to a realization.
はじまりの樹が目覚める前に
絶園の樹を復活させ→
If the Tree of Exodus were revived before the Tree of Genesis awoke,
it could seriously damage the Tree of Genesis once more,
もう一度　深いダメージを与えて
再び長い眠りに就かせることを。
putting it back into its deep sleep.
まあ
本当に　それが実行されるとは→
But I never imagined that a plan had been set in motion.
思ってもみなかったけど。
軍隊を動かしてる
お偉いさんたち→
I doubt all the military higher-ups
まさか　この攻撃が　世界を
滅ぼすことになるかもなんて→
have any idea that their attack could lead to the end of this world.
考えてないだろうな。
（葉風）左門　それは
幾度となく　一族で論じた。→
Samon, we have debated this matter as a clan on numerous occasions.
（通信）
いくら　この世が不完全といえ→
No matter how incomplete this world is,
the Tree of Genesis will not rewrite the whole world.
はじまりの樹は
世界を丸ごと書き換えはせん。→
It will merely fix points that need addressing.
問題点のみを修正するだけだ。
そこへ　絶園の樹で
深い衝撃を与えてしまっては→
If you use the Tree of Exodus to try to damage the Tree of Genesis,
it's possible that even I will be unable to control the ensuing chaos.
それによって　私でも
制御できない暴走が起こりかねん。
それこそ
あらゆる生物が死に絶える。
That is what will cause mass extinction!
姫様
あなただけが　そう主張された。
Princess,
you were the only one who believed that.
ですが…→
However,
we, as a clan, have already decided.
もはや
一族で　答えは出ているのです。→
どのような犠牲を払おうと
我々は→
We must fulfill our duty, regardless of the cost.
務めを全うしなければならない。
（葉風・通信）おごるな！
Enough with your pride!
The Kusaribe clan is supposed to follow the Tree of Genesis!
はじまりの樹の従者たる
鎖部の民が→
What good can come from opposing it?
その主に背いて　なんとする！
It is to protect this world!
この世界を守るためです！
従者たれど
我らは　樹の奴隷ではありません！
We may be its followers, but we are not its slaves.
I'm saying you cannot protect the world that way!
だから　それでは　世界は守れん！
（左門）どうする？　少年。→
What will you do, young man?
Will you side with the princess, even after hearing that?
これを聞いても
まだ姫様の味方をするか？→
判断を誤れば
お前たちが　この世界を滅ぼすぞ。
If you choose wrongly,
you will destroy this world.
≪どうするって
いきなり　そんなの…≫
What do you mean, what will we do?
≪魔法について　詳しく
知ってるわけでもないし→
It's not like we know that much about magic.
二人の人間性を
知ってるわけでもないし→
Nor do we know what kind of people these two are.
どっちが正しいなんて
決められるわけ…≫
There's no way we can judge who's telling the...
へっ！
まあ　どっちが正しくてもいいや→
I actually don't care who's right.
俺には関係ねぇし。
えっ？
I really don't give a crap.
What?
おい　真広。
それに→
Hey, Mahiro...
Not to mention that Hakaze told me long ago that you guys could be right.
お前らの方が正しいかもって話は
とうに　葉風から聞いてる。
Nothing's really changed now that you've told me again.
もう一回　聞かされても
何も変わらねぇよ。
いや
そんな話　僕は聞いてないって。
Wait, this is the first I've heard any of this...
そりゃあ　聞かせてねぇから。
えっ？
That's because we didn't tell you.
お前が聞いたら
ぐだぐだ迷って面倒だしな。
If we had, any second thoughts of yours would have been annoying.
（左門）お前は
姫様の言葉を疑わなかったのか？
You didn't doubt the princess's words?
別に　お前の言葉も疑ってねぇよ。
It isn't that I doubt your words, either.
説得力は　どっちもどっちだろ。
The two of you are about as equally persuasive.
はぁ…
人間的に　どうかと思うが→
You have to wonder about him as a person.
But he honestly doesn't care what happens to this world.
（通信）その者は　この世のことなど
気にしておらん。→
That said, Samon,
故に左門　貴様の負けだ。
you lose.
≪「おれは
どん底に降り立っている→
Conscience and grace, to the profoundest pit.
この世もあの世もあるものか」≫
I dare damnation. To this point I stand
that both the worlds I give to negligence.
≪「知ったことか。　どうともなれ」≫
Let come what comes, only I'll be revenged.
≪「ただ…
ただ復讐さえすればいいのだ」≫
世界の心配は　あとだ。
I'll worry about the world later.
さあ　葉風を戻せよ。
Now, get Hakaze back...
There's someone she needs to find for me!
俺は　あいつに
見つけてもらうヤツがいる。
さあ　葉風を戻せよ。
Now, get Hakaze back...
≪世界の命運を気にかけぬ者…≫
Someone who doesn't care what happens to the world.
To think someone like that ended up with the princess.
≪そんな者が
姫様とつながるとは…。→
いや　そんな者の存在自体→
No, the fact that someone like him even exists
世の理が
姫様の味方をしている証しか…≫
may be proof that the logic of the world is siding with her.
（左門）お前の望みはなんだ？→
What is your wish?
世界を滅ぼす危険を顧みず
誰を求める。
Whom do you seek, even if it means
the world's destruction?
Bring Hakaze back here, and you'll find out.
葉風が　ここに戻れば分かるさ。
You don't need to know yet.
お前は　まだ知る必要ねぇよ。
（左門）姫様が戻れば…　か。→
If I bring back the princess...
そうか　ならば　やむをえん。
Very well.
Then I have no other choice.
（葉風）これで詰みだ。
This would be checkmate,
Samon.
左門　終わったな。
This ends it.
≪とはいえ　真広の妹が
１年前に殺されていなければ→
However, if Mahiro's younger sister hadn't been killed a year ago,
it's unlikely he would have ever thought of revenge,
真広は　復讐を考えず
私に手を貸すことも→
こうして　左門に揺るがぬ態度を
とることもなかったろう。→
and thus been able to aid me and to talk to Samon that way.
Looking at it another way,
捉え方によれば　真広の妹は→
it could be said that Mahiro's younger sister was killed for my sake...
私のために殺されたとも言える。→
Regardless, she died before I was brought to this island.
しかし　殺されたのは
私が　ここに放り出される前だ。→
はじまりの樹が　私のために
そう仕組んだわけはあるまい≫
I doubt that the Tree of Genesis planned that out for my sake.
≪これでいいのか？
葉風さんが　世界を救うならいい≫
Is this how it should be?
This was fine if it allowed Ms. Hakaze to save the world.
But if Samon is right,
≪でも　左門って男の
言うとおりだったら→
it's Ms. Hakaze who will destroy the world.
葉風さんは
この世界を滅ぼしてしまう≫
≪それを　真広個人の望みで
決めていいのか？≫
Should the world's fate be determined by Mahiro's personal desires?
真広　お前は
世界を救ってやるって言ったろ？
Mahiro...
Didn't you say you were going to save the world?
下手すれば
その逆になるかもしれないんだぞ。
If we're not careful, the exact opposite could happen.
Do you think that makes any sense?
それは　理にかなってるのか？
ふっ。
If this world is correct for the most part,
この世界が
おおむねでも正しいなら→
葉風を戻しても滅びやしねぇよ。
bringing Hakaze back won't destroy it.
でも
どうしようもなく間違ってれば→
But if it's all wrong, wouldn't it be better
一度　滅んで造り直した方が
よっぽど正しくねぇか？
for it to be destroyed, to start anew?
≪そうか…≫
I understand...
More than anything...
≪真広にとって
愛花ちゃんを殺した　この世界は→
Mahiro hates this world
because it killed Aika.
とにかく気に入らないんだ≫
In his mind, he doesn't care how it's corrected, so long as it is.
≪どんな形であれ
修正されるなら→
筋が通ってるって考えてるんだ≫
≪無理だ≫
It's impossible.
≪僕が真広を
どうこうできるわけがない≫
I won't be able to stop Mahiro.
≪愛花ちゃんのために
何ができるか→
I don't even know what I can do for Aika.
僕には分かりもしないのに…≫
Come on, Kusaribe Samon...
ほら　鎖部左門→
Hurry up and bring Hakaze back.
さっさと　葉風を戻せよ。
ドシューー！
バシューー！
ボゥン　ボゥン　ボゥン！
（部下）結界の第１層に変化！
There's a change in the first layer of the barrier.
Return! Return! Return! Return!
（男たち）戻れ　戻れ　美しい…。
Beautiful! Beautiful! Beautiful!
（部下）現状が続けば
結界の消失は　時間の問題です！
If things continue,
the barrier's destruction will be inevitable!
夏村！
ヤツらの兵器を塵にしてくれ！
Natsumura, turn their machines to ash.
３割だ。
それで　軍は立ち行かなくなる！
Just a third.
That should hold off their army.
（夏村）委細承知。
Understood.
（左門）少年　一つ問う。
Young man,
I ask you this.
姫様が　お前の望みを
かなえられなければどうする？
What will you do if the princess is unable to grant your wish?
例えば→
For example, what if the princess were already dead?
姫様が
すでに死んでいるとすれば。
ふっ　例え話は
リアリティーがあるのにしろよ。
If you're gonna ask "what if," at least come up with a realistic one.
（左門）十分リアルだ。→
It is very real.
（通信）姫様は　すでに死んでいる。
ん？
The princess is already dead.
（左門）見るがいい！
See for yourselves!
樹の中の樹　大樹の中の大樹→
Tree within the tree,
great tree within the great tree.
Hear my words, and grant my wish.
我が言葉において聞き届けよ。
（左門）姫様は
このように骨となっている。
As you can see, the princess has been reduced to nothing but bones.
お前の望みをかなえる力はない。
She has no power to grant your wish.
我々の邪魔をしても
お前が得るものは何もないのだ。
You gain nothing from getting in our way.
（潤一郎）((僕は
彼女の遺体を確認したんだ))
I verified her body.
It was instinct,
((直感的に分かった→
これは葉風ちゃんだって))
but I knew it was Hakaze.
Those are Ms. Hakaze's bones?
≪あれが葉風さんの骨？
いやいや　そんなわけないって≫
No, that can't be.
（葉風・通信）左門　こうして
今　貴様と話している私が→
Samon, there's no way I can be dead if I'm talking to you right now.
死んでいるわけなかろう。
よもや貴様
この私を幽霊とでも言うのか？
Are you actually going to try claiming that I'm a ghost?
（左門・通信）いえ。
No.
However, I have your full skeleton here.
しかし
これは　あなたの全身骨格です。
I brought this, as well as the barrel,
私が　この手で　この樽と共に→
back from the island myself.
孤島から持ち帰りました。
Samon, what are you trying to say?
（葉風）左門　貴様　何が言いたい。
That must be the skeleton Juniichiro said he saw.
≪潤兄さんが
見せられたという骨か≫
What is he trying to accomplish by bringing that out now?
≪あれを
ここで持ち出して　何を…≫
姫様　今は何年です？
Princess, what year is it?
何？
What?
（左門）その島で過ごされて
４か月ほどだそうですが→
You say you've spent about four months on the island.
今　西暦で言えば何年です？
Right now, what is the year, by the Christian calendar?
今は　西暦…。
Right now, it's...
ピシャーン！（雷鳴）
（葉風）どうした。→
What's the matter?
（通信）
何か　おかしなことを言ったか？
Did I say something odd?
葉風さん　それ→
Ms. Hakaze,
that was two years ago...
（通信）２年前の西暦ですよ？
（葉風）２年？→
Two years...
２年過ぎている？
バカを言うな。→
Two years have passed?
Don't be ridiculous.
私は　この島で　４か月ほどしか
過ごしておらんぞ！→
I've only spent about four months on this island.
いくらなんでも
まるまる２年も勘違いするか！
There's no way I'd mistake two years for four months!
どういうことだ？
What's going on?
姫様…→
Princess...
そこは
我々にとって　２年前の世界です。
Your world is two years in our past.
姫様からすれば
こちらは２年後の世界。
To you, our world is two years in the future.
（左門）
魔法による交信方法でなければ→
If you hadn't been exchanging messages through magic,
this wouldn't have ever been possible.
（通信）まず　こんなことは
起こらなかったでしょう。
With the power of magic,
魔法によって
今現在と２年前のその島が→
the present has been connected to your time on that island
時間を越えて
つながっているのです。
by traveling through time two years into the past.
時間を越えて!?
Traveling through time?
ピシャーン！
kimi to miteta nagareboshi oikakete
Chasing the shooting star that we saw together
Reaching this place all alone
hitori bocchi konna toko made kiteta
Hiding the feelings I wanted to express to you
kinou kimi ni ienakatta kimochi o
kotoba no naka kakusu no
within words
tooku hanarete itemo douka todokimasu you ni
No matter how far we are separated,
please let it reach you
kono michi no saki ni matsu unmei nante
The fate waiting for us down this road
is not yet known
ima wa mada
dare mo mada
shiranai kedo
by anyone
To the future drawn by numbed fingers
kajikan da yubisaki de egaita mirai he
With you we can make it
kimi to nara ikerutte
nee sonna ki ga shiteta nda
That's what I feel
kitto
with certainty
Last name: Yamamoto.
First name: Evangeline.
（山本）
姓は山本　名はエヴァンジェリン。
Oh, just die there.
ああ　そこで勝手に死んでろ。
What... What's going on?
（左門）
なんだ？　何がどうなっている!?
So this is where you and Mahiro kill each other because of me.
（愛花）
私のせいで　真広と吉野さんが→
I can't believe it...
殺し合う展開ですね。
（葉風）信じられん…。
Mahiro,
I'll tell you the identity of Aika's boyfriend.
真広　お前に→
愛花ちゃんの彼氏が誰だったか
教えてやる。
Episode 9
Boyfriend